<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?><w:document xmlns:w='http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main'><w:body><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Squadron 42 Community Bot – User Guide</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>This guide explains how to use the Squadron 42 Community Bot. Each section summarises what the bot automates, which slash commands configure the feature, and what permissions you need.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Getting Started</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Invite the bot with both applications.commands and bot scopes, and grant Manage Channels, Manage Roles, message content, and Read Message History permissions.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Slash commands register when the bot boots. If a command is missing, verify permission to manage commands and restart the bot.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Configuration Status</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Command: /config-status (Administrator)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Posts an embed summarising ticket lobbies, voice templates, Spectrum watcher settings, embed upload allow-list, referral pool stats, org promotion forums, and moderation automation. Run this first when validating a deployment.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Ticket System</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /ticket set-channel, /ticket set-archive, /ticket roles add|remove|list (Manage Guild)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Members click the ticket lobby embed to create a private channel with staff. Closing a ticket archives the channel into the configured category.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Dynamic Voice Rooms</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /voice-rooms set-template, /voice-rooms clear-template, /voice-rooms list (Administrator)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Designate lobby voice channels that spawn personal rooms when joined. Empty rooms are deleted automatically.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Embed Template Uploader</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /embed-access add|remove|list (Manage Server)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Upload a .txt/.md file that follows the Embed Template Instructions. Allow-listed roles have their templates rendered as embeds; plain text without template markers is reposted as normal messages. Users without access have their upload removed and receive a direct message explaining the policy.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Referral Pool</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /register-referral-code, /get-referral-code (Everyone)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Stores and distributes STAR referral codes. Messages containing raw codes are removed and the user is reminded to use the slash commands.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Moderation Suite and Org Monitoring</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /mod roles add|remove|list, /mod auto-ban set|clear|status, /mod org-promos add|remove|list; context actions Warn, Kick, Ban, Timeout, View History; /pardon (Manage Guild/Administrator as appropriate).</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>The bot routes slash and context commands through dedicated handlers. Auto-ban traps ban users when a trap role is applied. Org promotion enforcement deletes links posted outside authorised forums, prunes empty threads, and prevents duplicates. Referral/org monitoring runs on every message to keep channels compliant.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Spectrum Watcher</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Commands: /spectrum set-channel, /spectrum set-forum, /spectrum status, /spectrum clear, /spectrum post-latest (Manage Guild)</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Polls a configured RSI Spectrum forum and posts new threads into the chosen Discord channel. /spectrum post-latest forces a manual repost.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Troubleshooting Checklist</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Missing commands: restart the bot after confirming it can manage slash commands.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Ticket lobby not responding: rerun /ticket set-channel and check the bot can create channels.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Voice rooms persisting: confirm the lobby is still configured and the bot can manage channels.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Spectrum posts absent: run /spectrum status, then rerun set commands if needed.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>• Template upload rejected: have an admin run /embed-access add &lt;role&gt; for your role.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val='Heading1'/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>Support</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>Contact a server administrator or consult the Squadron 42 Bot repository for updates and support.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr><w:pgSz w:w='12240' w:h='15840'/><w:pgMar w:top='1440' w:right='1440' w:bottom='1440' w:left='1440'/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>